=Demon Emperor's Little Matchmaker=
= صانع الثقاب الصغير للإمبراطور الشيطاني =
=Episode 10=
= الحلقة 10 =
Oh no, this time you must...
أوه لا ، هذه المرة يجب عليك ...
Sorry, I didn't know you're...
آسف ، لم أكن أعرف أنك ...
Carry on. I'll be back later.
الاستمرار في.  سوف اعود لاحقا.
No need.
لا حاجة.
Chuchu, go back for now.
تشوتشو ، عد الآن.
Remember to come over to massage me tonight.
تذكر أن تأتي لتدليك لي الليلة.
Okay.
تمام.
Stop looking.
توقف عن النظر.
She's long gone.
لقد ذهبت منذ زمن.
I didn't expect Ms. Chuchu to be so attractive.
لم أكن أتوقع أن تكون السيدة تشوتشو جذابة للغاية.
She could even break this big iceberg.
يمكنها حتى كسر هذا الجبل الجليدي الكبير.
Have you two...
هل لديك اثنان ...
Have we what?
هل لدينا ماذا؟
Wuyou.
Wuyou.
Stop pretending.
كف عن التظاهر.
You have good connections outside the palace.
لديك اتصالات جيدة خارج القصر.
Investigate the source of this red rope for me.
تحقق من مصدر هذا الحبل الأحمر بالنسبة لي.
No problem.
لا مشكلة.
Another thing,
شيء آخر،
stop being busybody.
توقف عن كونك مشغولاً.
But you must promise me one thing.
لكن يجب أن تعدني بشيء واحد.
No way.
مستحيل.
I haven't even mentioned what it is.
لم أذكر حتى ما هو عليه.
You're too quick in rejecting.
أنت سريع جدًا في الرفض.
Ms. Chuchu.
السيدة تشوتشو.
Yueying.
يويينج.
Thank you, Ms. Chuchu.
شكرا لك السيدة تشوتشو.
Thank me?
اشكرنى؟
Since you're here,
بما أنك هنا ،
Young Master has changed.
لقد تغير السيد الشاب.
Really?
هل حقا؟
But he still looks cool to me.
لكنه لا يزال يبدو رائعًا بالنسبة لي.
I've been following Young Master for many years.
لقد كنت أتابع المعلم الصغير لسنوات عديدة.
I've never seen him so cheerful
أنا لم أره قط بهذه البهجة
and personable.
وأنيق.
It's all your credit, Ms. Chuchu.
كل الفضل لك ، السيدة تشوتشو.
How...
كيف...
How was he then?
كيف كان بعد ذلك؟
I know what you want to say.
انا اعرف ماذا تريد ان تقول
Rong family has been protecting the Demon Emperors for generations.
تحمي عائلة رونغ أباطرة الشياطين لأجيال.
They've protected us for over a thousand years.
لقد قاموا بحمايتنا لأكثر من ألف عام.
Yueying isn't just my servant,
يويينج ليس خادمي فقط ،
she's also my family.
إنها أيضًا عائلتي.
Hence unless she agrees,
ومن ثم ما لم توافق ،
I won't give her to anyone.
لن أعطيها لأي شخص.
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
It's the Empress.
إنها الإمبراطورة.
What's the matter?
ما الأمر؟
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
The matter in the courtyard is settled.
تتم تسوية الأمر في الفناء.
We've fulfilled my duty
لقد أوفينا بواجبي
and we're not sorry to the late princess.
ونحن لا نأسف للأميرة الراحلة.
I get it.
أحصل عليه.
In fact,
في الواقع،
it's difficult for the girl.
من الصعب على الفتاة.
Should we
هل ينبغي لنا
reward her with more jewelries?
تكافئها بالمزيد من الحلي؟
Do as you see fit.
افعل ما تراه مناسبًا.
Your Majesty, there's another thing.
جلالة الملك ، هناك شيء آخر.
Our second son, Wuming,
ابننا الثاني ، وومينغ ،
is at the age of marriage now.
في سن الزواج الآن.
Your birthday will be in a few days.
عيد ميلادك سيكون في غضون أيام قليلة.
I wonder if we should
أتساءل ما إذا كان ينبغي لنا
invite the daughter of the prime minister over...
دعوة ابنة رئيس الوزراء فوق ...
I get it.
أحصل عليه.
Do as you see fit.
افعل ما تراه مناسبًا.
Yes, Your Majesty.
نعم يا صاحب الجلالة.
I see.
أرى.
(No wonder Li Wuyou has such an indifferent and sad look.)
(لا عجب أن لدى Li Wuyou نظرة حزينة وغير مبالية).
(Turns out he has been very lonely.)
(اتضح أنه كان وحيدًا جدًا).
(Since Ms. Yueying cares so much about Li Wuyou,)
(بما أن السيدة يويينج تهتم كثيرًا بـ Li Wuyou ،)
(I wonder if the two of them...)
(أتساءل ما إذا كان الاثنان ...)
Ms. Chuchu.
السيدة تشوتشو.
I can tell that Young Master likes you a lot.
أستطيع أن أقول أن السيد الشاب يحبك كثيرًا.
Please...
لو سمحت...
make him happy, okay?
اجعله سعيدا ، حسنا؟
You said he likes
قلت أنه يحب
me?
أنا؟
♪The wind of the early summer♪
رياح أوائل الصيف ♪
♪Created a starry sky♪
♪ خلق السماء المرصعة بالنجوم
♪The dream in my heart♪
الحلم في قلبي ♪
♪Froze at the street intersection in the morning♪
تجمد عند تقاطع الشارع صباحا
♪I've passed the end of the galaxy♪
♪ لقد اجتزت نهاية المجرة ♪
♪I've seen the crowded traffic♪
♪ لقد رأيت ازدحام المرور ♪
♪In my mind♪
♪ في ذهني ♪
♪Your smile is engraved♪
♪ ابتسامتك محفورة ♪